Gradey Cullins

Software Developer

Seasoned computer programmer with a hunger for growth and success.

Demonstrable track record highlighting a broad variety of hard and soft skills related to professional computing. Professional experience ranging from established corporate environments to disruptive startups.

Work History

2018-01 - Software Engineer

Hoodoo Digital, Salt Lake City, UT

- Full stack programmer with a variety of responsibilities:
 - develop and maintain a SPA written in Vue.js
 - develop and maintain a CLI tool written in Node.js
 - develop and maintain a Web API server in Golang
 - integrate above projects with Docker and Kubernetes, write dockerfiles and make deployments and updates to multiple k8s clusters
- Represented Hoodoo as on-site software engineer at Western
 Digital to develop a pixel- perfect, mobile-first site.

2017-05 -2018-01

Full-Stack Web Developer

Navitaire, Salt Lake City, UT

- Contribute to and debug variety of internal and external enterprise software w/ 10k+ LoC
- Contribute to and test C# / .NET e-commerce backend
- Development on enterprise-scale SPA written in Angular.js
- Update and maintain large MSSQL databases including making schema updates, cloning and restoring large tablesets

Education

2013-01 -2018-01

BS: Computer Science

University Of Utah

- Wide diversity of CS electives including Computer Networks,
 Operating Systems, and graduate-level Data Mining
- 1st place senior capstone project
- Peer-to-peer file storage system

Contact

Address

Salt Lake City, UT, 84102

Phone

(208) 201-7901

E-mail

gradeycullins@gmail.com

Skills

Javascript

00000

Python

00000

Shell

00000

Java

00000

Golang

C#/.NET

••••

SQL

••••

NoSQL

••••

Docker

00000

Kubernetes

00000

Data science

00000